♪
[chuckles softly]
[CHA] What exactly do you think
you're you doing?
I asked you a question.
It shouldn't be
that difficult to answer.
♪
[Jinwoo sighs]
[JINWOO]
That was careless.
I should have seen this coming.
I was trying
to find my way back
but, uh, I think I got lost.
[CHA]
You're lost?
Hmm,
you're with the mining team.
Look, beyond there
is the boss room.
You should stay clear.
[JINWOO]
Hae-in Cha.
The rumors about her were true.
I didn't notice her presence
until she spoke.
[gasps]
[CHA]
I swear I saw it.
Wasn't he holding
a weapon a moment ago?
Sorry about that.
[CHA] You need
to leave this place now.
If you accidentally
agitate the boss,
the entire mining team
could be wiped out.
[JINWOO]
Yes, ma'am.
[footsteps approaching]
Uh.
Wait, hold on!
Yes?
[footsteps approaching]
[gasps]
[sniffs]
[CHA] For some reason,
he doesn't stink.
[JINWOO]
Is everything okay?
I'm sorry,
but are you really a hunter?
[JINWOO]
Um, yeah?
[CHA]
Jinwoo Sung,
an E-rank.
[clears throat]
Never mind, sorry.
You should be careful
on your way back.
This dungeon is pretty big.
Ah, sure thing.
[footsteps receding]
[CHA] Is it
because his rank is so low?
He didn't smell bad.
If anything,
he smelled nice.
[YOONSEOK]
I still can't believe
you ran into Hunter Cha.
You sure are lucky.
Even getting the chance
to just talk to her
is a pipe dream
for people like us.
[chuckles]
You laugh, but...
she's no joke.
Patrolling nonstop
in case the dungeon boss
goes on a rampage.
She's something else, that one.
[JINWOO]
So that's what she was doing.
[JINSOO]
You know what I heard?
Apparently, she doesn't like
the way other hunters smell.
[JINWOO]
The way they smell?
Huh.
Guess that sense
is stronger for her?
You ever noticed
how she's always
covering her nose?
[JINWOO]
Oh, yeah.
But the way she reacted,
maybe...
I don't have the scent
of a typical hunter?
Wait, typical hunter?
That red gate boss
said something similar.
Is it because I'm the Player?
[sighs]
Having the system's assistance
does set me apart.
But...
what even is the "Player?"
[YOONSEOK]
You did a good job today.
[JINWOO]
Thank you, sir.
We'd still be at it
if not for you.
I can't believe we wrapped up
before the collection team
finished.
It's like you were born
to be on the mining team!
Unless, maybe
you had an excavator
hidden away somewhere.
[JINWOO]
Oh, man, if only.
I've been doing this work
for a while now,
and I've never seen anybody
with a knack for it
like you've got.
[JINWOO]
Oh!
[clears throat]
That's why...
I'd like to offer you
a permanent spot.
You'll be paid handsomely!
Thank you, but...
I'm afraid I can't accept.
I'm only here
because I had some free time.
Hmm.
I understand.
Well, that's a real shame.
But ya know, what do you say
to coming in for
just one more day, then?
-You need more help?
-[YOONSEOK] Yeah.
We've got a double-header
scheduled for tomorrow,
one A-rank and one C-rank.
[JINWOO] My reassessment
is in a couple of days.
I was able to earn the money
I needed today, so...
Wait, did he say...
There are gonna be two
Hunters Guild raids tomorrow?
C-rank and an A, right?
[YOONSEOK] Yes.
Although,
it'll be our secondary
strike team running the show.
You got another strike team?
Sure do! That's one
of our greatest strengths.
There aren't
many domestic guilds
that can dedicate two teams
to taking down A-rank gates.
[JINWOO] Okay,
where am I meeting you then?
Huh. I figured
you'd turn me down, for sure!
Right! I'll make sure you get
paid double the usual wage!
[JINWOO] Wh...
No, no, I can't take that.
[YOONSEOK] Just take it!
You work so fast,
it's the least I can do!
[CHA] Yes,
I'm looking for a file, please.
One of the hunters working
with the mining team today
named Jinwoo Sung.
[MALE ASSOCIATE 17A]
The E-rank hunter?
[CHA]
You already know of him?
[MALE ASSOCIATE 17A] Oh, well,
it's just that Guildmaster Choi
asked me to get his file, too.
[CHA]
Do you know why?
[MALE ASSOCIATE 17A]
Sorry, ma'am, I don't.
But Hunter Sung's details
are unavailable.
[gasps]
It's strange, the Association
has a lock on his file
as if he's a top-level hunter.
[CHA]
I see, thank you.
[CHA] The way
he was acting in the dungeon,
the fact
that the guild master's
looking into him.
The Association's involvement.
Something's going on here.
Out of all of the hunters
I've ever come across.
Jinwoo Sung is the first one...
who ever smelled nice to me.
[YOONSEOK] Oh!
There you are!
Mister Sung!
[JINSOO]
It's good to see you again!
Oh.
[SANGSHIK]
Hey, kid.
Have you eaten yet?
[CHIYUL] Jinwoo!
Good to see you.
[JOOHEE] Try not to
get hurt today, okay, Jinwoo?
[footsteps approaching]
[indistinct chatter]
[JINWOO]
This feeling.
I'd forgotten what it was like.
[JINSOO]
When it's time for lunch,
you should join us!
[YOONSEOK] Uh-huh!
We'd love to have you!
-[JINWOO] Sure. I can do that.
-[YOONSEOK] Great.
[YOONSEOK] All right,
first up is the C-rank dungeon!
The strike team should be
coming out soon, so get ready!
[digging]
[JINSOO] Impressive as ever,
Mister Sung!
[chuckles softly]
The work just gets done faster
with you around.
It'll be nice
having a chance to rest
before hitting
the A-rank dungeon.
[YOONSEOK] The collection team
couldn't believe it either.
Are you sure you don't want
to come work with us?
Five times the pay!
[sighs]
I can't, I can't.
-[KIHOON] Excuse me.
-Huh?
[YOONSEOK]
Captain Kihoon Son.
[KIHOON] I was wondering
if you could lend us
someone from the mining team.
The guy who was supposed be
our carrier never showed.
But from the miners?
Wouldn't someone
from the collection team
be better suited?
Apparently, they're already
short staffed as it is.
[YOONSEOK]
Hmm.
If you choose
to accept the job offer,
I'll make sure you're given
hazard pay for your trouble!
[indistinct chatter]
Carrying equipment in
an A-rank dungeon
is too dangerous.
Respectfully, sir.
We can't spend the money
if we're dead.
[KIHOON] So, no one here's
willing to help us?
[JINWOO]
I'll do it.
-[gasps]
-No way!
[YOONSEOK] Wait!
Mister Sung!
Do you wanna die?
You know how strong
the magic beasts are in there?
Even with the hazard pay,
it's not worth the risk!
[JINWOO]
Eh, I'll be fine.
I'm a lot braver than I look.
[YOONSEOK]
I don't doubt that,
but this isn't
a question of courage, kid!
Sir, he only
just started yesterday,
he doesn't understand
what he's agreeing to!
-What's his rank?
-[JINSOO] He's E-rank.
Please, you should
find someone else.
It's fine.
I'd like for him to do it.
[both gasp]
My name's Kihoon Son.
I'll be taking point
with the strike team
on today's raid.
And I'm Jinwoo Sung.
The gate's bigger
than yesterday's.
[KIHOON]
That may be true,
but it's emitting
much less magic power.
I wouldn't worry too much.
If there was anything
really dangerous in there,
the primary team
would be sent to handle it.
[JINWOO] Six A-ranks.
And three B-ranks.
No one here is an S but,
in any other guild
these hunters wouldn't be
relegated to a secondary team.
[KIHOON]
All right, let's get going!
[JINWOO] Their guild's even
stronger than I realized
if they can field
two teams of this level.
Hm.
There really is less
magic power in the air
compared to yesterday.
But...
something's off.
I have that same bad feeling
I did when I entered
the red gate.
Am I imagining it?
-No need to be nervous, okay?
-Hm?
Kihoon...
[gasps]
I mean the captain
and everyone else
are superb hunters.
As long as you don't run off,
the magic beasts won't have
an opening to attack you.
Hm.
Good to know, thanks.
[KIHOON]
Once this raid is over,
I'll officially make leader
of the secondary team.
I might not be
the strongest in the guild,
but I am one
of best A-rank hunters around.
I can handle this!
Uh!
[JINWOO]
No orders needed,
just instinct.
♪
Here they come!
[growling]
Dungeon jackals!
[grunts]
♪
[slicing]
My turn.
[growling]
Duck!
[grunts]
[groans]
[growls]
♪
[KIHOON] Why are jackals
in an A-rank dungeon?
Is it that unusual
to find them in here?
Dungeon jackals are
C-rank magic beasts.
An A-rank food chain
should've wiped them out.
[JINWOO]
Collars?
Captain.
Maybe these aren't
just wild jackals.
[KIHOON] Is it possible
they were kept as hunting dogs?
Hmm?
[rumbling]
[JINWOO] There's the reason
behind that bad feeling.
[stomps]
[growls]
[GEONGUK]
High orcs?
[MYUNG-CHUL]
Why are they here?
[roaring]
[grunts]
[thuds]
[crashes]
[KIHOON]
They aren't playing around!
[yells]
[grunts]
[GEONGUK]
My taunt skill didn't work!
It's targeting the back line!
Look out!
[fire roaring]
[groans]
You'll have to
try a little harder!
[groans]
[growls]
[SEOKJIN]
No effect.
How high is
their magic resistance?
♪
[straining]
[strains]
It's a powerful one!
I can only hold it
for a few seconds!
That may be all we need!
You who I now awaken.
Collect the head of my foe!
[growls]
[grunting]
[SEOKJIN] My secret weapon
costs a ton of mana,
but it's worth it!
[grunts]
[slides]
[growls]
[thuds]
[groans]
[grunts]
[GINA]
Healer!
-We need help!
-I hear you!
One second!
We're outnumbered!
And it'll just get worse
if they surrounded us!
Spread out into
groups of three!
Go!
[KIHOON] Even one high orc
is a match for an A-rank.
So what hope
do the B-ranks have?
Against this many?
[swords clanks]
[growls]
[screaming]
[KIHOON] Come on.
Stay with me, you guys!
[growls]
[Bora grunts]
[grunts]
[groans]
All right!
Who's next?
I've got you!
Try to stay still.
♪
[stomping]
[growling]
Uh...
[exhales]
[orc groans]
[gasps]
[groaning]
[choking]
[squelching]
[thuds]
[blood dripping]
[SEMI]
Di-did that just happen?
[grunts]
Uh!
[yells]
[pants]
What changed?
Why are they suddenly
moving slower?
[grunts]
-[GEONGUK] Push 'em back!
-[Gina yells]
All the way back!
[JINWOO] Hate to butt in
as an outsider, but...
I can't just let them die.
[swings]
[yells]
[slicing]
[JINWOO] No one would mind
if I weaken them a bit.
[stabs]
Hold still for a sec, would ya?
[grunts]
[yells]
[explodes]
[chuckles]
[thuds]
[grunts]
[blood dripping]
[Kihoon yells]
[screams]
[thuds]
[screaming]
[slices]
[orc groans]
[shudders]
[breathes deeply]
[gasps]
[thuds]
[panting]
[KIHOON]
Any mortal wounds?
[MYUNG-CHUL] No. Nothing
our healer couldn't handle.
[GEONGUK]
Which is an absolute miracle.
Hey.
Did you notice anything weird
toward the end of the fight?
Yeah, the orc I was fighting
got sluggish all of a sudden.
That was all your doing,
right, Gina?
No, don't look at me.
I've just got attack magic
and telekinesis.
None of the spells I know
can slow things down.
And all of the other mages here
are fire-focused.
Yes, that's some kind
of stealth skill.
No one on our squad
has that ability.
[BORA]
But, who cares how we won?
The point is we did.
Yeah, you're right.
Let's chalk it up to good luck.
[BORA]
Does he think we're stupid?
Well, joke's on him, I guess.
All these mages around,
and he actually believed
no one would
notice him using Stealth.
Tricks aside,
he did help us
out of a tight spot.
I'm sure he has his reasons,
so I won't out him for now.
[MYUNG-CHUL]
Do we press on, captain,
or is a retreat in order?
[KIHOON]
Hmm.
[GEONGUK] This is too risky
for our strike team.
We definitely need
two more healers,
and another three mages,
at least.
Look, it's a shame this is
how your first raid as captain
wound up going,
but I feel like
the smartest move here
is to withdraw.
[exhales]
[JINWOO] I get
what a tough decision this is.
He obviously wants
to clear this dungeon.
But, if he's
a reasonable leader...
Right.
Let's fall back
for the time being!
[BORA]
Hm.
[sighs]
[GEONGUK] Oh, good. I was
worried you'd wanna keep going.
I might be ambitious,
but I'm no idiot.
-[gasps] A barrier?
-[electricity crackling]
[BORA]
A strong one.
Wasn't here before.
[EUNSOO] Yeah, it would've
been kinda hard to miss.
What now?
With enough time
I think I can dispel it.
[BORA] Something with
incredible magic made this,
and it's still lurking.
Turning back
was the right call.
The more I see,
the more I realize
we can't clear this place.
[MYUNG-CHUL] This power.
Where is it from?
[EUNSOO]
Nowhere good.
[GEONGUK]
The dungeon boss?
Hurry and give me some support!
-[GINA] You got it!
[SEOKJIN] Here!
[JINWOO]
A wave of magic
strong enough
for B-ranks to detect.
But nobody could sense it
from the outside?
[squelching]
[retches]
[groaning]
[KIHOON] A curse?
No! We're trapped!
Semi, holy magic, now!
Semi?
What are you...
[gasps]
[stomping]
[MYUNG-CHUL] I count at least
50 of these guys, captain.
[gasps]
-Kihoon, wait...
-[KIHOON] I know.
But if we fight them,
we'll end up dead, so...
[speaking in unknown language]
[ALL ORCS]
♪
[KARGALGAN]
Greetings, humans.
I am called Kargalgan.
My vessel will lead you
to come meet with me.
Kargalgan?
That barrier's your handiwork,
isn't it?
[KARGALGAN]
It is, indeed.
I am a proud
orcish master of curses.
[KIHOON] And are you
the master of this cave,
or is there someone stronger?
[Kargalgan chuckles]
[KARGALGAN] Do you truly think
any exist who could surpass me?
[KARGALGAN]
Now, choose.
Will you be killed
by my soldiers,
or will you agree
to come meet with me?
[breathes shakily]
We'll meet with you.
[footsteps receding]
Hunter Sung.
[JINWOO]
Yes?
[footsteps approaching]
Since this guy's
most likely the boss,
we'll attack
as soon as we see him.
Even with his strength,
I doubt he can
maintain his barrier
and fight with us
at the same time.
That'll be
your chance to escape.
Contact the main strike team.
Don't tell me
you're planning to die here.
The plan's still the same,
ensuring this gate
closes in time.
Whether we survive or not.
Hey, um, would you mind
doing me a favor?
Hm.
[SEMI]
It's not much, but...
my will is in here.
Please take it to my family.
We're hunters.
This is what
we're trained to do,
but your case
is a little different.
So if you can, get out alive.
[JINWOO]
Death breathing down your neck.
No options but bad ones.
Just like the double dungeon
where I was...
abandoned.
But these people are different.
[sighs]
I'll still hold onto it
for now but,
hopefully, it doesn't
come to that.
[chuckles softly]
[CHA]
I don't see him.
Did he quit mining work
after one day?
That you, Hunter Cha?
Uh.
What brings you by?
Thought you were off.
Well, um,
I was looking for
the new recruit, Jinwoo Sung.
[YOONSEOK] Ah.
Yeah, he's around.
Got roped into helping out
as a carrier today.
[CHA]
Oh, he did?
Then he's inside
of the gate right now.
♪
[KARGALGAN]
I bid you welcome.
Human worms.